bitrefill.com 2017-03-19

# Bitrefill - Recharge prepaid phones with Bitcoin

The following provisions makes out the current privacy policy issued for the mobile top up services offered through the website www.bitrefill.com (in the following **"Website")**. The services offered through the Website (in the following **"Services"** ) are provided by Pupot AB, a limited company incorporated under the laws of Sweden (in the following **"Bitrefill","we","us","our"** ). By visiting the Website and using the Services you expressly agree with the provisions expressed below as well as the Bitrefill Terms of Service.

If you for any reason object to and do not agree with this policy you are not allowed to access and use the services we provide and we ask you to refrain from doing so.

**What data does Bitrefill collect?**

There are two types of data that Bitrefill needs to collect from you:

**Personal Data**  
Personal Data is any type of information that identifies you or can be used to identify you as an individual. You acknowledge and agree with that we may collect and process the following Personal Data related to you: 

  * Your e-mail address.
  * Your IP address.
  * Other information you from time to time provide by registering such data in forms on the Website.
  * Information we’ve requested in relation to you reporting a problem with the Website and/or the Service.
  * In the case you contact us we may also keep a record of the information you have supplied us with in the correspondence.
  * Details of the Top-Up transactions you carry out on.

We also collect and process the receive mobile telephone number that you provide to us. This is necessary to facilitate the sending of the Top-Up to that number.  

**Non-Personal Data**

Like most other websites, Bitrefill gathers information for statistical and analytical purposes.   
We referred to this as Non-Personal Data. To further explain Non-personal data is information that cannot be used to identify or contact you. The data we collect and process in this regards includes the type of browser you use and other statistical data relating to the use of the Website and our Services. Information may also include content you view, such as which operator and country, the date and time that you view this content.

**Why does Bitrefill collect this Non-Personal Data?**

The team behind Bitrefill is always looking to improve the Website and Services in order to provide you as the customer with the best experience possible. We always strive to deepen our understanding of where our customers come from, what they appreciate and what parts of Bitrefill they feel can be improve on. Collecting and processing the above specified data is an important if not vital mean of achieving this objective.

We also use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements. We collect information about where you saw the ads we serve and what ads you clicked on.

As you browse the Website advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with the Website. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address or telephone number. You can visit this page to opt out of AdRoll’s and their partners’ targeted advertising.

**How do we use your Personal Data?**

You acknowledge and agree with that we may use this Personal Data for the following:

  * To enable us to help you execute the Top-Up order that you have requested and to process any payment connected with that Top-Up request.
  * To contact you if it's required in relation to the Top-Up that you have sent or to reply to any communications that you from time to time might send to us.
  * To provide you with information on products or services that might interest you.
  * To notify you about any changes to the Website or Services.
  * To ensure that content on the Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer.
  * To provide you with highest level of customer care we possibly can.
  * For marketing analysis.
  * For security purposes, i.e. to prevent fraud and other illegal activities in relation to usage of the Website and/or the Services.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file of letters and numbers that is stored by the browser on your computer when you visit certain websites. A cookie allows a website to distinguish your computer from other users’ computers. Normally cookies do not contain Personal Data unless you have already given this information to the Website.

We use cookies in order to be able to present the Website in the most suitable fashion possible and to make sure that we receives the most relevant data from our database while you are visiting the Website.

**Does Bitrefill give Personal Data to third parties?**

For instance when you use the Services, we will disclose the receiving mobile telephone number(s) to the relevant mobile service distributor(s) and/or operator(s). This is completely necessary in order to execute the Top-Up order that you have requested. This is completely necessary in order to execute the Top-Up order that you have requested.  
As stated above we might however share certain data with third party service providers in our ambition to ensure fully operational Services as well as enabling an efficient communication stream with our users. 

We may disclose your Personal Data if we are required to comply with any applicable law, a summons, a warrant, a court or regulatory order, or other statutory requirement. In the case we have reason to suspect any form of illegal interaction with the Website and/or usage of the Services we also reserve the right to, on a voluntary basis, share your Personal data with relevant law enforcement agencies. We will always respect your privacy as long as you respect our Terms of Service and any applicable law(s).

**Does Bitrefill give Non-Personal Data to third parties?** **  
** We may provide Non-Personal Data to third parties (for example mobile operators) regarding the number of unique users who visit our Website, the demographic breakdown of users of our Website, or the activities of users on our Website.

**What can be learned from Non-Personal Data?**

There are a lot of useful things to be learned from this information. For example, it can help potential advertisers, providers of advertising services, commercial partners, sponsors, licensees, researchers and other similar parties.

**Will Bitrefill use my Personal Data for direct marketing purposes?**

We may use your Personal Data to send you information by SMS or email relating to our products and services which may be of interest to you or similar products and services to those you have previously purchased from Bitrefill.

Bitrefill does not sell or share your Personal Data or CPNI data with subsidiary companies or third parties for marketing or profit purposes.

**Can I opt-out?**

You can opt-out at any time, free of charge, by contacting Bitrefill via email. If you for any reason would like to do so or if you have any questions and/or comments about this policy please send us an email at [support@bitrefill.com](mailto:support@bitrefill.com).
